Guide to the James and Margaret Goff Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Collected Material, Series VI
  - Conferences
    - National Study Conference on Church and State (NCC), Columbus, Ohio, 1964 Feb 4-7 (Box 27, Folder 570)
    - CICOP-2nd Annual Conference, Latin America and the Universal Church, 1965 Jan 29 (Box 27, Folder 571)
    - Sixth World Order Study Conference, 1965 Oct 23 (Box 27, Folder 572)
    - Presbyterian Consultation on "New Work", Tijuana, Mexico, 1967 Apr 12-13 (Box 27, Folder 573)
    - Coemar Fall Conference, Chicago, IL, 1967 Aug 24-30 (Box 27, Folder 574)
    - U.S. Conference on Church and State, Detroit, MI, 1967 Oct 22-26 (Box 27, Folder 575)
    - I Consulta de Asociaciónes de Seminarios Evangelicos de América Latina, Montevideo, 1967 Dec 19 (Box 27, Folder 576)
    - Congreso Eucaristico Internacional, Bogotá, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 577)
    - Racism and a City in Motion Conference (UCSD), San Diego, CA, 1968 Sep 21 (Box 27, Folder 578)
    - Primer Congreso Nacional de Teología, Mexico, 1969 Nov 25 (Box 27, Folder 579)
    - CICOP-7th Annual Conference, New Dimensions in Hemispheric Realities, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 580)
    - World Affairs Council Conference, Latin American Radicalism and the American People, Cambridge, MA, 1970 Feb 28 (Box 27, Folder 581)
    - Law and Social Change Bossey Consultation (WCC), 1970 Jul 19-24 (Box 28, Folder 582)
    - Tercer Seminario Latinoamericano, Geneva, 1970 Sep-Dec (Box 28, Folder 583)
    - Refugee Consultation (CWS/NCC), 1970 Dec 16 (Box 28, Folder 584)
    - CICOP-8th Annual Conference, Freedom and Unfreedom, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 585)
    - Consultation on University Ministriesand Latin American Policy Study, Ithaca, NY, 1971 Mar 19-21 (Box 28, Folder 586)
    - Interamerican Communication Seminar (CELAM/USCC), Mexico City, 1971 May 19-25 (Box 28, Folder 587)
    - Interamerican Communication Seminar (CELAM/USCC), Mexico City, 1971 May 19-25 (Box 28, Folder 588)
    - Interamerican Communication Seminar (CELAM/USCC), Mexico City, 1971 May 19-25 (Box 28, Folder 589)
    - Interamerican Communication Seminar (CELAM/USCC), Mexico City, 1971 May 19-25 (Box 28, Folder 590)
    - Interamerican Communication Seminar (CELAM/USCC), Mexico City, 1971 May 19-25 (Box 28, Folder 591)
    - Study-Conference on Peace and Justice in the Western Hemisphere, Washington, D.C., 1971 May 26 (Box 28, Folder 592)
    - Working Committee on Church and Society, Nemi, Italy, 1971 Jun (Box 28, Folder 593)
    - Primer Comgreso Nacional Joven Poesia, Santo Domingo, D.R., 1971 Jul (Box 28, Folder 594)
    - Caribbean Ecumenical Consultation for Development, Port of Spain, Trinidad, 1971 Nov 15-21 (Box 28, Folder 595)
    - Congressional Conference on U.S.-Cuba Relations, 1972 Apr 19-20 (Box 28, Folder 596)
    - Third United Nations Conference on Trade and Development (UNCTAD 111), Santiago, Chile, 1972 Apr (Box 29, Folder 597)
    - Congreso Internacional de Nutricion, Mexico, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 902)
    - Taller de Relaciones Humanas, Oaxtepes, Mexico (CAVE), 1973 Apr 24-30 (Box 29, Folder 599)
    - International Women's Year Tribune, Mexico city, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 903)
    - Religious Studies I, Ecumenical Institute, Chicago, IL (Box 29, Folder 600)
  - Organizational Materials
    - Christians Associated for Relations with Eastern Europe (CAREE) Conference, 1989 Oct 27-28 (Box 29, Folder 601)
    - Center for the Study of Development and Social Change, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 602)
    - Centro de Planificacion y Accion Ecuménica (CEPAE) (Box 29, Folder 603)
    - Centro Intereclesial de Estudios Teológicos y Societes, 1987 (Box 48, Folder 904)
    - Christian Action for Development in the Caribbean (CADEC), 1972 (Box 29, Folder 604)
    - Circulo de Oración Pro Bolivia 'Chasqui', 1973 Jun-Aug (Box 29, Folder 605)
    - Clergy and Laity Concerned (CALC), 1984, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 606)
    - Comisión Evangélica Latinoamericana de Educación Cristiana (CELADEC), 1972 (Box 29, Folder 607)
    - C.C.I.A. (Commission of the Churches on International Affairs), 25th Executive Committee Meeting Background Dossier, 1970 Jun 19-23 (Box 29, Folder 608-614)
    - Conferencia Episcopal para la Iglesia en el Ecuador (Box 48, Folder 905)
    - Concilio Nacional Evangelico del Peru, 1962-1968 (Box 48, Folder 906)
    - Consejo Episcopal Latinoamericano, Boletín, 1968 Jul-Aug (Box 29, Folder 615)
    - Difusiones Interamericanas Resumen de La Telecomunicación Evangélica, 1970-72 (Box 29, Folder 616)
    - Ecumenical Program for Interamerican Communication and Action (EPICA), 1970-72, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 617)
    - Federación Evangélica de Mexico, 1968-1971 (Box 29, Folder 618-619)
    - Haitian Research Center for Sosial Sciences (CHISS), 1972 (Box 30, Folder 620)
    - Hispanic-American Institute, 1967, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 621)
    - Iglesia Metodista en Argentina Uruquay, Bolivia (Box 48, Folder 907)
    - Instituto de Estudios y Accion Social (IDEAS), 1992 (Box 30, Folder 622)
    - International Forum on Globalization, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 908)
    - Interreligious Foundation for Community Organization (IFCO), 1990-94 (Box 30, Folder 623)
    - IFCO, 1995-2000 (Box 30, Folder 624)
    - Office of Worldwide Evangelism-in-Depth Latin American Mission Reports, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 625)
    - Latin American Studies Assoc., 1971 (Box 30, Folder 626)
    - La Liga Argentina de Cultura Laica, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 909)
    - Morimiento de Reconciliacion en la Argentina, 1968 (Box 48, Folder 910)
    - NCC-Church World Service Disaster Reports, 1970-73 (Box 30, Folder 627)
    - NCC-Church World Service Misc., 1970-73 (Box 30, Folder 628)
    - NCC-Division of Overseas Ministries Misc., 1966, 1967, 1972-73, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 629)
    - NCC-General Board, 1965, 1968, 1969, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 630)
    - NCC-Health Care Coverage, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 631)
    - NCC-Latin American Department/Working Group, 1967-72 (Box 30, Folder 632)
    - NCC-Latin American Working Group, 1973-74 (Box 30, Folder 633)
    - Peace with Justice Coalition and Center, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 634)
    - Presbyterian Church, USA-Latin American affairs, 2003, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 911)
    - PRISA, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 635)
    - Spanish Language Institute, Costa Rica, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 912)
    - Sociedad Internacional de Libertad Religiosa Seccion Colombo-Venezolana, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 913)
    - Union Latinoamericana de Juventudes Ecumenicas (ULAJE), 1973 (Box 30, Folder 636)
    - United Nations, 1960-67 (Box 30, Folder 637)
    - UPCUSA-Board of National Missions (Amplify Newsletter), 1969-73 (Box 30, Folder 638)
    - UPCUSA-Board of National Missions, Dept. of Missions Development, 1968-71 (Box 30, Folder 639)
    - UPCUSA-COEMAR Mexico Mission (John Hazelton), 1969-70 (Box 30, Folder 640)
    - UPCUSA-COEMAR General, 1962-70 (Box 30, Folder 641)
    - UPCUSA-183rd General Assembly, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 643)
    - UPCUSA-Program Agency/Misc., 1981 (Box 30, Folder 644)
    - UPCUSA-Program Agency (formerly COEMAR) Handbook, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 645)
    - UPCUSA Misc., 1969- 1976 (Box 31, Folder 646)
    - U.S. Congress, 1965, 1969-73, 1989, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 647)
    - U.S. State Department, 1963, 1964, 1970-72, 1987, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 648)
    - WCC-Secretariat for Relationships with Christian Councils (Box 31, Folder 649)
    - World Council Meeting 69 (John Coventry Smith) (Box 31, Folder 650)
    - WCC Misc. (Box 31, Folder 651)
    - World Literacy and Christian Literature: The Word at Work, 1969 Oct-1973 Jul (Box 31, Folder 652)
  - Articles
    - Africa (Box 31, Folder 653)
    - Brazil (Box 31, Folder 654)
    - Central America (Box 31, Folder 655)
    - Chile (Box 31, Folder 656)
    - Columbia (Box 31, Folder 657)
    - Cuba (Box 32, Folder 658)
    - Cuba (Box 32, Folder 659)
    - Guatemala (Box 32, Folder 660)
    - Latin America (Box 32, Folder 661)
    - Latin America (Box 32, Folder 662)
    - Mexico (Box 32, Folder 663)
    - Mexico (Box 33, Folder 664)
    - Mexico (Box 33, Folder 665)
    - Nicaragua (Box 33, Folder 666)
    - Panama (Box 33, Folder 667)
    - Quincentennial (Box 33, Folder 668)
    - Quincentennial (Box 34, Folder 669)
    - U.S.A. (Los Angeles) (Box 34, Folder 670)
    - Uruquay (Box 48, Folder 914)
    - Articles-Misc. (Box 34, Folder 671)
  - Newspaper Clippings
    - Clippings, 1940-49 (Box 34, Folder 672)
    - Clippings, 1950-1957 (Box 34a, Folder 707)
    - Clippings, 1958-1968 (Box 34, Folder 673-678)
    - Clippings, 1968-1969 (Box 34a, Folder 708-709)
    - Clippings, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 679-680)
    - Clippings (Spanish), 1969 (Box 35, Folder 681-682)
    - Clippings, 1970-1989 (Box 35, Folder 683-693)
    - Clippings, 1990-1993 (Box 36, Folder 694-700)
    - Clippings, 1993-1996 (Box 37, Folder 701-706)
  - Subject Files (Early Career)
    - Argentina - "Boletín Informativo de Legislacion Argentina" 5 issues, 1955 (Box 48, Folder 915)
    - Book Catalogs/Notices (Box 38, Folder 707-709)
    - Book Reviews, 1964-72 (Box 38, Folder 710)
    - Bible Study Materials, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 711)
    - Bibliographies, 1960, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 712)
    - Bolivia, Human Rights, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 713)
    - Bolivia - "Vision Evangélica" - periodical issue, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 916)
    - Chile, Religion and Education, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 714)
    - Chile - "Tribuna Evangélica" - 4 issues, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 917)
    - Chile -"Politica y Espiritu" - two periodical issues, 1955 (Box 49, Folder 918)
    - Church Bulletins, 1958-70 (Box 38, Folder 715)
    - Chile - Catholic Church, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 919)
    - Colombia, Church in (Misc.), 1957, 1958 (Box 38, Folder 716)
    - Colombia, Church in, 1960-69 (Box 38, Folder 717)
    - Colombia, Map of Churches, n.d. (Box 38, Folder 718)
    - Communism, 1955 (Box 49, Folder 920)
    - Cuba, Iglesia Presbiteriana-Reformada, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 719)
    - Cuba, Unpublished Reports, 1969-71 (Box 38, Folder 720)
    - Cuba Newsletters, 1967-73 (Box 38, Folder 721)
    - Cuba Journal/Magazine Articles, 1964-72 (Box 38, Folder 722)
    - Cuba, 100 Years of Struggle Resource Packet (Box 38, Folder 723)
    - Cuba Misc., 1968-1973 (Box 39, Folder 724)
    - Davis, Angela (Legal Defense), 1971 (Box 39, Folder 725)
    - Directories (Box 39, Folder 726)
    - Dominican Republic, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 727)
    - Drug Abuse, 1970-71 (Box 39, Folder 728)
    - Ecology, 1970-71 (Box 39, Folder 729)
    - Economic Justice-U.S., 1971 (Box 39, Folder 730)
    - Ecuador - pamphlet "Imagen del Ecuador" Press release, 1963, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 921)
    - Evangelismo y Mayordomia, 1957, 1958 (Box 39, Folder 731)
    - Fraternal Workers in Colombia, 1964-65 (Box 39, Folder 732)
    - Guatemala-Human Rights, 1971-72 (Box 39, Folder 733)
    - Illich, Ivan, 1967, 1969, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 734)
    - "Jesuchristo en el Mexico", 1973 (Box 39, Folder 735)
    - 'Jesus People', 1971-72 (Box 39, Folder 736)
    - Korea-Arrest of Christians (Rev. Park H. Young-Kyu, et. al-Notes and Correspondence), 1973 Jul, Oct (Box 39, Folder 737)
    - Local Church Cooperation (U.S.A.), 1969, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 738)
    - Mass Media, 1971-72 (Box 39, Folder 739)
    - McGovern, George, Latin American Task Force, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 740)
    - Menstruation Educational Materials (Spanish), n.d. (Box 39, Folder 741)
    - Mexico, Church in (Misc), 1970-73 (Box 39, Folder 742)
    - Mexico (Misc.), n.d. (Box 39, Folder 745)
    - Missionary Role, 1969-71 (Box 40, Folder 746)
    - New Churches (USA), 1970-71 (Box 40, Folder 747)
    - "Rebel Priests" (Notes, Drafts), 1969 (Box 40, Folder 748)
    - Religious Liberty in Latin America, 1945-68 (Box 40, Folder 749)
    - Refugees, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 750)
    - Rockefeller Family Tree (Box 40, Folder 751)
    - Song Sheets-Spanish, 1950-59 (Box 40, Folder 752)
    - Song Sheets-Spanish, 1950-59 (Box 40, Folder 753)
    - Song Sheets-English, 1929-1957 (Box 48, Folder 890)
    - Stewardship CELADEC Pamphlet, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 754)
    - Stewardship Handbooks/Reports, 1950-1969 (Box 40, Folder 755)
    - Miscellaneous, 1950-69 (Box 40, Folder 756)
    - Stewardship Tracts, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 757)
    - Third World Cinema, 1970-79 (Box 40, Folder 758)
    - Tracts, Misc., 1952, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 759)
    - Vietnam War, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 760)
    - Volunteerism (Peace Corps), 1970 (Box 40, Folder 761)
  - Subject Files (Later Career/Retirement)
    - Central America, Washington Office Memos (PC(USA)/Kermit Johnson), 1989-90 (Box 41, Folder 762)
    - Central America (PC(USA) Responses), 1987-90 (Box 41, Folder 763)
    - Central America, U.S. Government Documents, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 764)
    - Central America, Peace Process, 1989 Jul-1990 Apr (Box 41, Folder 765)
    - Central America, Peace Process, 1990 May-1993 Dec (Box 41, Folder 766-767)
    - Central America, Misc., 1985-1996 (Box 41, Folder 768-770)
    - Chiapas, Mexico, 1994-1998 (Box 41, Folder 771-772)
    - Church Bulletins, 1992, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 773)
    - Columbus Quincentenary, 500 Años de Resistencia, 1990-1992 (Box 41, Folder 774-775)
    - Columbus Quincentenary, Centro Regional de Informaciones Ecuménicas, 1990 Nov-1992 Jan (Box 41, Folder 776)
    - Columbus Quincentenary, Latin American Council of Churches '500 Years', No.1-6 (CLAI), 1991 Apr-1992 Sep (Box 41, Folder 777)
    - Columbus Quincentenary, CLAI 'Rapidas', No. 224-233, incomplete, 1991 Oct-1992 Aug (Box 41, Folder 778)
    - Columbus Quincentenary, Jubilee Commission, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 779)
    - Columbus Quincentenary, NCC Study/Action Packet, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 780)
    - Columbus Quincentenary, Ecumenical Press Service/Latin American EcumenicalNews/Latin American Links/Challenge in Central America, 1992/1992/1989/1992 (Box 42, Folder 781)
    - Columbus Quincentenary Misc., 1992 (Box 42, Folder 782)
    - Consistent Life Ethic, 1989, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 783)
    - Cuba, IFCO Materials, 1992-99 (Box 42, Folder 784)
    - Cuba, Misc., 1990-2000 (Box 42, Folder 785)
    - El Salvador, 1989-1994 (Box 42, Folder 786-788)
    - Guatemala, 1989, 1991, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 789)
    - Menchu, Rigoberta, 1992-94 (Box 42, Folder 790)
    - Nicaragua Election, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 791-792)
    - Nicaragua Election, Center for International Communication, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 793)
    - Nicaragua Election Reports, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 794)
    - Nicaragua Election, Consejo Supremo Electoral, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 795)
    - Nicaragua Election, Nicaraguan Embassy Press Agency, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 796)
    - Nicaragua Election Watch, Reports, etc., 1990 (Box 43, Folder 797)
    - Nicaragua Election, Reports, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 798)
    - Nicaragua Election, Misc., 1990 (Box 43, Folder 799)
    - Nicaragua, Nicaragua-U.S. Friendship Office, 1992-2000 (Box 43, Folder 800-801)
    - Nicaragua, PEACENET Updates, 1990 Dec (Box 43, Folder 802)
    - Nicaragua, Misc., 1985-1996 (Box 43, Folder 803-805)
    - Nicaragua, Misc. (includes J.E.G. notes), n.d. (Box 43, Folder 806)
    - North America Free Trade Agreement, 1991-93 (Box 43, Folder 807)
    - Panama (Operation Just Cause), 1989-91, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 808)
    - Panama - children's book, 2000 (Box 49, Folder 922)
    - Poverty, 1993-94 (Box 43, Folder 809)
    - Refugees, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 810)
    - School of the Americas, 1993-94 (Box 44, Folder 811)
- Personal Items and Memorabilia, Series VII
  - Biography (Box 44, Folder 812)
  - Dictation (Box 44, Folder 813)
  - Health (Box 44, Folder 814-815)
  - Photographs (Box 44, Folder 816)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 44, Folder 817)
  - J and M. Goff Travel brochures (Box 44a, Folder 886)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 44a, Folder 887)
  - Miscellaneous incl. calling cards, receipts, etc. (Box 44a, Folder 888)
  - Jesuit Poster vs. JEG B/Q, 1959 (Box 44a, Folder 889)
  - Photograph album, n.d. (Box 44a, Folder 890)
  - Mexico (Box OV1)
  - Mexico (Box OV2)
  - Cuba (Box OV3)
- Addendum -2010, Series VIII
  - Costa Rica
    - Fact sheet and newspaper clippings, 1991, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Cuba
    - Center for Cuban Studies newsletter, 1988, 1992, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Food First newsletter, 1994, 2000 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Global Exchanges newsletter, 1993-1995, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - International Peace for Cuba Appeal newsletter, 1993-1995 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous newsletters, 1990-1997, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Gramma International newspaper, September 1994-April 1995 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Gramma Weekly Review newspaper, 1983, 1988 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Signs of Transition: 80's Art from Cuba, 1988 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Cuba bibliography, September 20, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - The Disarm Education Fund: Cuban Medical Project (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Human Rights, 1989, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Inttereligious Foundation for Community Organization: Leadership Summit on Cuba, July 27,1993 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - The Church and Cuba, newspaper clippings, pamphlets, 1977-1994 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Fidel Castro, newspaper clippings, pamphlets, 1977, 1983, 1990, and n.d. (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Healthcare in Cuba, newspaper clippings, pamphlets, 1982. 1992, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous, newspaper clippings, pamphlets, 1984-1994. n.d. (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - U.S. - Cuba Foreign policiy, newspaper clippings, pamphlets, 1981-1995, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - U.S. Trade Embargo Against Cuba, newspaper clippings, pamphlets, flyers, 1993-1995, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Pamphlets about 1993 Cuban elections (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Pastors for Peace: Freedom to Travel Challenge, 1993 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Personal accounts/reflections on traveling to Cuba, 1981-1990, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Travel information for Cuba, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - United Church Board of World Ministries: Cuba Strategy Meeting, February 19, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - U.S.-Cuba Friendshipment, 1993,1995 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - El Salvador
    - Miscellaneous newsletters, 1988-1996 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Salvanet: The Newsletter of CRISPAZ, 1991-1996 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Booklets incl. Managing the Facts: How the [U.S] Administration Deals with Reports on Human Rights Abuses in El Salvador, 1980-1981, 1985 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Assasination of Priest Oscar Romero, newspaper clippings, 1980, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Christians for Peace in El Salvador fund raising letters, 1993-1995 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - CISPES (U.S. Committee in Soldarity with the People of El Salvador) fund raising letters, 1991-1996 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Essays on Protestanism in El Salvador, January 1992 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Human Rights, news clippings, 1989-1990 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous newspaper clippings, 1980, 1992-1994 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - News updates, brochures, fund raising letters from various non profit organizations, 1981, 1989, 1994-1995 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Periodicals with articles pertaining to El Salvador, 1980, 1990, 1992, 1993 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Road map and fact sheet, 1979-1980 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Solidarity work incl. U.S. legislative alerts, flyers, and fundraising letters from non-profit organizations, 1989-1993, and n.d. (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - U.S. Foreign policy with El Salvador, 1987-1990 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Guatemala
    - Guatemala: The Bulletin of the Guatemala Human Rights Commission/USA newsletter, 1994-1997 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Guatemala Review newsletter, 1991-1994 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Human Rights Violations, 1990-1996 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous newsletters, 1991-1997 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Noticias de "Guatemala Hoy" newsletter, 1998 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Report on Guatemala serial, 1991-1995 and 1999 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Booklets incl. Memorandum to Government of Guatemala, Cry for the Land, and Refugees and Repatrification, 1986, 1987, 1988, and n.d. (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence from missionaries, 1995, 1996 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Fundraising letters from non-profit organizations, 1991-1997 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous newspaper clippings, 1991-1995 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Nobel Peace Prize winner Rigoberta Manchu Tum newspaper clippings, 1992-1993 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Haiti
    - Miscellaneous, 1989, 1994, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Honduras
    - Booklets incl. With the Miskitos in Honduras, The Situation of Human Rights in Honduras 1987, and The Situation of Human Rights in Honduras 1991, 1986, 1987, 1991 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Mexico
    - Viva Chiapas! newsletter, 1994-1996 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Immigration issues in the United States, 1980, 1991, 1995-1996 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous, 1991-1997 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Rebellion in Chiapas, Mexico, 1994-2000, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Nicaragua
    - Bulletin of NICCA (Nicaragua Center for Community Action) newsletter, 1989, 1993-1994 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Friendship Findings: Nicaragua-Pomona Valley Friendship Project Newsletter with brochures and flyers, 1990-1995 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Informes CAV (Servicio del Centro Ecmenico Antonio Valdvieso) newsletter and pamphlets, 1981-1983 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous newsletters, bulletins, and periodicals, 1984, 1987, 1989, 1991-1992 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Nicaragua Farmers' View newsletter, 1994-1995 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Nicaragua Monitor newsletter, 1990-1995, 2003 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Nicaragua Network News newsletter, 1987-1990 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Nicaragua Network Subscriber Service newsletter, 1989-1990 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Nicaraguan Developments newsletter, 1994-1997, 2003 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Pastors for Peace newsletter, 1991, 1995 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Servicio Evangelico de Prensa newsletter, Julio 1991-Deciembre 1991 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Background Information, 1985-1987, 1989 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Background Information (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Booklets incl. The Attack on Pantasma, Nicaragua and Cronica de una Guerra no Imaginara, 1983, 1985, 1986 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Booklets incl. Violations of the Laws of War by Both Sides in Nicaragua in 1987 and Religion y Revolucion en Nicaragua, 1987, 1988, 1992, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - CEPAD (Council of Evangelical Churches of Nicaragua), 1984-1991, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - CEPRES (Comision Evangelica de Promocion de la Responsabilidad Social), 1988-1989 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - The Church and Theology in Nicaragua, 1990, 1991, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Constitution, 1984, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Contra War booklets incl. The Contra File and Terrorism: A Closer Look, 1982, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - 1987 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Contra War: Institute on Religion and Democrazy, 1984-1992 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Contra War: Newspaper clippings, pamphlets, periodicals, 1982-1992, n.d. (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - CUSCLIN Briefing book (Committee of U.S. Citizens Living in Nicaragua), 1986 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - CUSCLIN songs and statements, 1984-1986 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Dossier on Church and State in Nicaragua by the Ecumenical committee of U.S. Church personnel in Nicaragua, February 1985 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Daniel Ortega newspaper clippings, 1987, 1989, 1990-1993 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Election Nicaragua 1990: The Process at Work, 1989 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Elections, 1984, 1989-1991 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Fact sheets, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Flyers on Nicaraguan issues, presentations, or trips to, 1989, 1991, 1999, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Human rights, 1986-1989, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Manual CIA, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Maps, 1984, 1989, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 6)